You You pride yourself on being
versatile and also like being
you know attacking in the run
game too Where did that come
from? Yeah Um it's really just I
think just being an undersized
tight end a little bit to be
honest Um not being a liability
on you know first and second
down uh you know being able
to do a little bit cuz it also
helps the team out too and helps
myself out. It's it's rare you
see a a pass catching tight end
that also really likes to get
kind of dirty with the blocking
Yeah. Where does that come from
Is that that I mean is that
aggressiveness Is that violence
as you find it back in high
school Was an escape to get the
football Where did that aspect
of your game come from? Yeah I
mean you kind of you touched on
a little bit of all those pieces
You know I think one I've kind
of always had it Um I think it's
a bit just how I think the game
should be played you know kind
of like love aggression passion
all those things But um like I
said it really just comes down
to how much I love the game you
know what I'm willing to do for
teammates and things like that.
What made you think when the
Jets called you that it was a
prank did the phone number not
register or would like even No
no I was just that was just like
my biggest fear Uh if you go
like what like was it like
Shador and like all that stuff
that happened with him it's just
like that that just be such a
it's such a moment full of so
many emotions You know it'd be
kind of a you know not a fun way
to you get a prank call stuff
like that But no obviously um
the call and everything
everything was amazing. And you
come from a small town in Idaho
I mean what does it mean to be
representing that I can't
imagine a lot of lot of guys
have made the NFL from there
Yeah Yeah Not too many Um but no
it's awesome Like I said you get
to represent something a bit
bigger than yourself So um it
means something to those people
back home and especially all the
people that have you know helped
me get get to this point It's
awesome. Did you realize right
away like when D got on the
phone that it wasn't like when
did you say okay I'm safe? Yeah
Um I mean it's really just why I
started started talking to each
individual coach you know and
management those things So um
but know once I really it kind
of hit me you know this isn't a
prank call this is the real deal
and I was super super excited.
Did you always play tight end?
Uh no no I put like like small
small ball I was like running
back Um and then once I got to
high school it was a receiver
and then college the tight end.
How did you how did you make
that move Like why why did did
they make that move? Yeah Um
obviously I think it's just kind
of where they saw my body kind
of transitioning to but also I
think another way to kind of
separate myself from you know
the other tight end I could have
done that at receiver but I just
think tight end kind of fits me
better as a person. Frank Reich
was pretty excited on that call
based on the video we saw Like
what what's been your
interaction with him you know
throughout this process? Yeah Um
we really only did like about
one Zoom meeting um with him and
you know we just kind of got to
know each other and then they
kind of you know talked
provisions they had you know
with the tight end room
including myself you know those
things So but no they're you
could definitely tell they're
great people to be around him
and Alfredo So I'm excited. Who
was some of your favorite tight
ends uh to watch kind of in N?
Yeah Um obviously George George
KD Uh George KD is probably my
favorite title to watch I like
watching Kyle Huch a lot They do
a really good job over there Um
obviously like like Coulson
Lovelin uh you know those guys
that have also also come from
Idaho which is pretty crazy Um
Kyle Pittz does a lot of a lot
of great things Um Evan Ingram
something like I got a lot of
comp too I've watched a lot of
of Evan Ingram I mean I really
try and watch everyone I've
watched Mason Taylor you know
I've watched Jeremy I've watched
both those guys and they both
did a really good job. Well for
you you know last year was you
know your first time getting
significant playing time for
Oregon so you had to like kind
of buy your time Like what what
was what kind of challenge was
that for you to obviously come
and and try to prove get your
chance now in the NFL like
pretty pretty quick turnaround
like what what was that journey
like for you having to b your
time at at Oregon? Yeah Um
obviously it went by really fast
but you know I wouldn't change
anything You know obviously I
got to sit behind some great
players like like Terrence
Ferguson and Patrick Herbert and
learn from them And then
obviously last year kind of take
the reigns of the offense And I
mean it was great Um you know
getting to help the young guys
out but also also kind of
showcase my abilities and you
know in the pass catching game
in the in the run game So no it
was great. I was reading like
you you designed workout plans
for people too How did that come
about Yeah Um I've always just
like loved working out in the
gym Um so you know I've she
started really in high school Um
you know start working out and
stuff and I'd always have have
like friends and stuff reach out
and like "Hey make me a plan?"
So I started making them plans
and stuff like that and it's
just something I kind of love
doing. You we we kind of live in
a day and and age in college
football now where if a player
isn't playing they leave and
they go somewhere where they are
playing You sat you learned you
developed and then when you got
your chance you you shine I mean
what what made you want to stay
What made you not want to leave?
Um I mean it was really I
definitely like contemplated it
at the time you know super easy
to do that but I just I kind of
found it more rewarding Um I I
kind of tried to you know beat
him out for his spot and um one
it made us closer and two I
think it made me a lot better Um
you know kind of made me focus
on what I needed to improve on
you know weaknesses in my game
game and you know kind of see
what he was better at than I was
And um no I think it was good um
mindset wise maturity wise but
also development wise. How much
much How much they playing at
Oregon especially against
talented players that are also
currently in NFL also help you
get to this point? Yeah I mean
you kind of said it's just like
the experience of playing
against high high level players
I think is huge You know at
those big schools like Oregon
Ohio State you know all those
schools you get a a good you
know sample size of what it's
going to be like The competition
competition piece Obviously it's
a lot different at this level
but you do get like a sample
size. You mentioned did it help
you running in the draft process
running 439 and 43.5 43.5 in
vertical Where do you think you
might have gone before that And
did it move you up the board you
think? Um I think it definitely
helped a little bit I mean not
anything crazy you know I think
people knew I was fast People
knew I could jump It was just
kind of putting the measurables
you know on paper you know
people kind of see what they're
working with But um I definitely
think it helped me a little bit
You know it was nice I don't
think people thought I was as
fast as I was um obviously So
kind of getting approved that
was good. What uh What was your
impression of the Angela Pods I
know you won against him Yeah
Indiana. Yeah obviously Um I
think that's a great pick Um I
think he's the best corner I
played against the year for sure
But But no I mean he's a bit you
can say on the underside size
too but um no it definitely
doesn't show it on the field You
know one thing I love about his
game is how much you know
passion and you know speed he
plays with So know it's awesome
to get a team up with him and
you know Cooper as well putting
against both of them twice So
know they're great guys. What do
you have to do Uh are you still
241 Is that that your weight? Uh
no I'll be I'll play this season
at like 2:45 to 247. So as a
blocker when you're when you're
not 260 what do you have to do
to compensate compensate for
that? Yeah Um obviously in my
game it's kind of huge pad level
um and speed to contact cuz
obviously I'm not um as tall as
one of those guys or big as some
of those guys using you know
know my little things that I
have whether that's pad leverage
or you know speed to contact
everybody good thank you
everyone awesome awesome